healthdev.net 2013-05-08

# Privacy & Cookies | Key Correspondents

The International HIV/AIDS Alliance (‘IHAA’) is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. For the purposes of the privacy policy, the term ‘Alliance’ refers to IHAA, its Country Offices, and its Linking Organisations around the world.

### Privacy Policy

This policy governs all pages hosted at www.keycorrespondents.org and registration for these sites. It does not apply to pages hosted by other organisations to which we may link and whose privacy policies may differ. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated. This policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically.

### Personally identifiable information

When you register to use the website – for example, subscribe to an e-bulletin or apply for a job – the Alliance collects the following information about visitors to the site: IP addresses; pages accessed; your location, operating system, etc and any information volunteered by you, such as an email address.

### Cookies

Like many websites, the Alliance uses cookies in order to provide you with a more personalised web service.

A cookie is a text-only string of information that we pass to your computer’s hard disk through your web-browser so that the website can remember who you are. Cookies cannot be used by themselves to identify you.

A cookie will typically contain the name of the domain from which the cookie has come, the “lifetime” of the cookie, and a value, usually a randomly generated unique number.

For more information about cookies, please see [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

If you do not wish to receive cookies you can easily modify your web browser to refuse cookies, or to notify you when you receive a new cookie. However, you may not be able to use all the interactive features of our site if cookies are disabled, and so in order to enjoy the Alliance site to the full, we recommend that you leave them switched on.

[Instructions on how to stop cookies being installed on your browser](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/)

### Use of information

The Alliance uses the information we collect about you to help us with understanding more about how our site is used, to make the site more useful, and to be able to send you relevant communications such as our e-bulletins.

### Collection of information

When you are on www.aidsalliance.org and are asked for personal information, you are sharing that information only with International HIV/AIDS Alliance, and its Country Offices and Linking Organisations around the world unless stated otherwise.

### Distribution of information

If you have subscribed to Alliance e-bulletins, we will send you regular communications as specified in the relevant area of the website. You are able to unsubscribe from any of the e-bulletins, or stop receiving Alliance publications, at any time by altering your preferences on this site (or by contacting the Alliance publications department).

### Changing and removing information

The accuracy of your individual identifying information is important to the Alliance. We are always looking for ways to make it easier for you to review and correct the information that the Alliance maintains about you through the Alliance website. If you change your email address, or if any of the other information we hold is inaccurate or out of date, please change it online, or email webmaster@aidsalliance.org. If you want us to stop using any information which you have provided in order to contact you, please also email webmaster@aidsalliance.org.

### Sharing information

Except as explained below, the Alliance will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information, and will not sell or rent lists containing your information to third parties. The Alliance may disclose information when it has your permission to do so or under special circumstances, such as when it believes in good faith that the law requires it. The Alliance may also use such information to contact individuals for marketing purposes.

### Information security

When you give the Alliance personal information we take steps to ensure that your information is treated securely. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be totally secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, the Alliance cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your information, we use our best efforts to ensure its security on our systems.

**June 2012**
